1. MIN, MAX, ABS
2. The distance between the two points. P1(x1, y1) P2(x2, y2).
3. A real number N. Find in a sequence of numbers sum(k - 4) k = 1,n /-3, -5, -6, -6, -5, -3, 0, 4, 9 .../ the first number is greater than N.
4. Check there is a point in a circle. Center C(x, y) radius - R.
5. Print the 1 - N(1, 2, .., N) numbers use recursion. 
6. Write the function which checks if number symmetric or not.(iteratively, recursively).
7. Given two variables, x and y, swap two variables without using a third variable.